You Have The Right To Remain Silent... FOREVER!
Maniac Cop 2 is a action, horror, thriller film directed by William Lustig.
Undead cop Matt Cordell rises from the grave, and is after
the criminals who murdered him in prison.
Det. Sean McKinney, played by Robert Davi.
Susan Riley, played by Claudia Christian.
Edward Doyle, played by Michael Lerner.
Jack Forrest, played by Bruce Campbell.
Teresa Mallory, played by Laurene Landon.
Matt Cordell, played by Robert Z'Dar.
Maniac Cop 2 is a 1990 American slasher film directed by
William Lustig and written by Larry Cohen.
It is a sequel to Maniac Cop (1988) and is the second
installment in the Maniac Cop film series.
It stars Robert Davi, Claudia Christian, Michael Lerner, and Bruce Campbell, with Robert Z'Dar returning as
Matthew Cordell, an undead police officer-turned-serial killer following his own murder.
Maniac Cop 2 was released direct-to-video in 1990, and received mixed-to-positive
reviews, with many considering it as an improvement over its predecessor.
It was followed by Maniac Cop III: Badge of Silence (1993).
The tone is dark and intense.